Guide to the Collection of Aerial Photographs 1935-2001
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Aerial Photographs and Orthophotos, 1935-2000; Series II
  - Stevens County, Washington, 1957-06-17; BBD (Box 035)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 28T; 29T; 30T
  - Stevens County, Washington, 1957-08-21; BBD (Box 036)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 30T; 31T; 32T; 33T; 34T
  - Wenatchee/Cle Elum, Washington, 1956-08-18; GS-VLH (Box-folder 037/01)
  - Wenatchee, Washington, 1963-09-07; WH (Box-folder 037/02)
  - Thurston County, Washington and other, 1978-05-18; NW-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Box-folder 037/03)
  - Cowlitz County, Washington (Toutle River), 1980-07-01; MSH-C-80 (Box-folder 037/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: B-1 thru B-11; 11-15
  - Skamania County, Washington (Swift Creek Reservoir and Dam), 1958; SCR (Box-folder 037/05)
  - Wahkiakum County, Washington, 1965-08-30; EOR (Box-folder 037/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2FF
  - Wahkiakum County, Washington, 1965-08-30; EOR (Box-folder 037/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3FF
  - Wahkiakum County, Washington, 1965-09-23; EOR (Box-folder 037/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4FF
  - Unidentified, 1954-1955; GS-VFB; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Box-folder 038/01)
  - King County Area, Washington, 1957-08-22; GS-VNU (Box-folder 038/02)
  - Pacific Crest Trail, King/Kittitas Counties, Washington, 1966-07-21; PCT-66 (Box-folder 038/03)
  - Wenatchee Lake Area, Washington, 1966-10-31; REC-17-6-1 (Box-folder 038/04)
  - Cady Pass, Washington, 1967-1968; L80084 (Box-folder 038/05)
  - Wenatchee Area, Washington, 1954-10-15; AV 140 (Box-folder 039/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 1
  - Wenatchee Area, Washington, 1954-10-15; AV 140 (Box-folder 039/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 2
  - Wenatchee Area, Washington, 1954-10-15; AV 140 (Box-folder 039/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 3
  - Wenatchee Area, Washington, 1954-10-15; AV 140 (Box-folder 039/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 4
  - Wenatchee Area, Washington, 1954-10-15; AV 140 (Box-folder 039/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 5
  - Lake Chelan Area, Washington, 1969-06-18; L90783; United States. Dept. of Agriculture (Box-folder 039/06)
  - Wenatchee National Forest, Washington, 1960-09-08; WEN R (Box-folder 039/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 1-10
  - Wenatchee National Forest, Washington, 1960-09-08; WEN R (Box-folder 040/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 11-19
  - Wenatchee National Forest, Washington, 1960-09-08; WEN R (Box-folder 040/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 20-29
  - Wenatchee National Forest, Washington, 1960-09-08; WEN R (Box-folder 040/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 30-42
  - Cascade Foothills, Western Washington from Canadian Border through Thurston County, 1965-09-07; WFPA-65; Washington Forest Protection Agency (Box-folder 040/04)
  - Cascade Foothills, Western Washington from Canadian Border through Thurston County, 1965-09-07; WFPA-65; Washington Forest Protection Agency (Box-folder 040/05)
  - Southwest Washington State, 1981-08-11; OSI-81; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Box-folder 041/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5-25-9; 5-25-10; 7-15-63
  - Clear Lake, Yakima County, Washington, 1966-08-19; REC-13-6-4 (Box-folder 041/02)
  - Wenatchee, Washington, 1942-09-04; GS-; Geological Survey (U.S.); Aero Service Corp. (Box-folder 041/03)
  - Wenatchee, Washington, 1942-09-04; GS-; Geological Survey (U.S.); Aero Service Corp. (Box-folder 041/04)
  - Wenatchee, Washington, 1942-09-04; GS-; Geological Survey (U.S.); Aero Service Corp. (Box-folder 041/05)
  - Wenatchee, Washington, 1942-09-04; GS-; Geological Survey (U.S.); Aero Service Corp. (Box-folder 041/06)
  - Index map for ERP-13-61; ERP-13-62; REC-13-63, ERP; REC (Box-folder 041/07)
  - Lake Pend Oreille; Albeni Falls, Idaho; (Photo Negatives), 1935 (Box-folder 041/08)
  - Alberta, Canada - Air Photos, Banff National Park, Undated; 83C, 83F, 83H, 83L; Alberta Government - Dept of Lands and Forests (Box-folder 042/01)
  - Series A-16037 to A-16042 (various); A16226; A-16980 to A16981 (various, Undated (Box-folder 042/02)
  - Laurd Reservoir, 1979-06-09; S79040-4 (Box-folder 042/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 202-207
  - Unidentified, 1984-07-10; GS-VFFX; GS-VFEX-C-81; GS-VFGE-C: GS-VFIE (Box-folder 043/01)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1987-08-08; GS-VFHA; GS-VFHB (Box-folder 043/02)
  - Wenatchee National Forest, Washington, 1975-08-12; 53037; USFS (Box-folder 043/03)
  - Unidentified, 1984-08-20; SLC-2; VAC-7 (Box-folder 043/04)
  - Colville Area, Washington, 1983-08-06; CIRW; BIA (Box-folder 043/05)
  - Unidentified, 1983-05-22; SW-H-83 (Box-folder 043/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 9W-34
  - Unidentified, 1980-09-16; OL-M-80 (Box-folder 043/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3B-1
  - Unidentified, 1985-08-16; 616030B; USDA-F (Box-folder 043/08)
  - Unidentified, 1984-06-25; SPS-8-2 (Box-folder 043/09)
  - Unidentified, 1984-06-18; Y (Box-folder 043/10)
  - Unidentified, 1983-07-11; C-R-8315 LC39 (Box-folder 043/11)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 30C-1; 31A-3
  - Unidentified, Undated; WSF-S-8 (Box-folder 043/12)
  - Unidentified, Undated; KC-S-9 (Box-folder 043/13)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 12-12 thru 12-22
  - Unidentified, 1957-09-13; GS-VRB (Box-folder 044/01)
  - Unidentified, 1953-08-13; GS WS (Box-folder 044/02)
  - Unidentified, 1953-09-04; GS WM (Box-folder 044/03)
  - Unidentified, 1973-06-04; FO-73 (Box-folder 044/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 44B-94; 44B-95
  - Unidentified, 1970-07-14; EWD (Box-folder 044/05)
  - British Columbia, Canada - Stereograms, Undated (Box-folder 044/06)
  - California/Nevada Weirds, Undated (Box-folder 044/07)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1968-06-18; FS-ERD (Box-folder 044/08)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1985-08-13; GS-VFGD (Box-folder 044/09)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1985-08-13; GS-VFGD (Box-folder 044/10)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1985-08-21; GS-VFGD (Box-folder 044/11)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1985-08-21; GS-VFGD (Box-folder 044/12)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1985-08-21; GS-VFGD (Box-folder 044/13)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1985-08-23; GS-VFGD (Box-folder 045/01)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1987-08-08; GS-VFGD (Box-folder 045/02)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1987-09-04; GS-VFGD (Box-folder 045/03)
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, Various; GS-VFGD (Box-folder 045/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Miscellaneous
  - Mt. Baker, 1991-07-23; 616050; United States. Dept. of Agriculture (Box-folder 045/05)
  - Mt. St. Helens - Color, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 045/06)
    Scale: 1:48,000
  - Mt. St. Helens, 1980-06-19; 616031; United States. Dept. of Agriculture (Box-folder 045/07)
  - Mt. St. Helens - Color, 1980-12-09 (Box-folder 045/08)
  - Mt. St. Helens, 1981; LVINV-81 (Box-folder 045/09)
  - Mt. St. Helens, 1981-07-27; LVINV-81 (Box-folder 046/01)
  - Mount Vernon, Washington, 12-01-1969; 06-01-1972; 2902-2903; 2902-3 - 2903-5 (Box-folder 046/02)
  - Monse, Washington, 1983-05-24; OC-C-83 (Box-folder 046/03)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 2), 1954-07-31; DVJ-2 (Box-folder 046/04)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 3), 1955-07-13; DVJ-3 (Box-folder 046/05)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 4), 1955-07-13; DVJ-3 (Box-folder 046/06)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 5), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 046/07)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 6), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 046/08)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 7), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 046/09)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 8), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 046/10)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 9), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 046/11)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 10), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 046/12)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 11), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 046/13)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 12), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 046/14)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 13), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 046/15)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 14), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 047/01)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 15), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 047/02)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 16), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 047/03)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 17), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 047/04)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Line 18), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1 (Box-folder 047/05)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan Project (Lines 2-18)(Second Set), 1954-07-31; DVJ-1, DVJ-2, DVJ-3 (Box-folder 047/06)
  - North Bend, Washington, 1964-07-25; KA-4-9 (Box-folder 048/01)
  - Mt. Baker Road Photos (Lines 1-10), 1961-07-10; MB (Box-folder 048/02)
  - Mt. Baker Road Photos (Lines 11-22), 1961-07-10; MB (Box-folder 048/03)
  - Okanogan National Forest, Washington (Lines 2 thru 3), 1970-07-07; EWC (Box-folder 048/04)
  - Okanogan National Forest, Washington (Line 4), 1970-07-07; EWC (Box-folder 048/05)
  - Okanogan National Forest, Washington (Lines 5-12), 1970-07-07; EWC (Box 049)
  - Okanogan National Forest, Washington (Lines 13 and 15), 1970-07-15; EWC (Box-folder 050/01)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington (Lines 1-6), 1939-08-01; GS-J; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Box-folder 050/02)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington (Lines 7-18), 07-24-1939 thru 09-25-1939; GS-J; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Box 051)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington (Lines 19-30), 07-25-1939 thru 10-12-1939; GS-J; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Box 052)
  - Olympic National Forest Roads (written on back of photos), Undated; OR-59 (Box-folder 053/01)
  - Olympic National Forest Roads (written on back of photos), Undated; OR-59 (Box-folder 053/02)
  - Olympic National Forest Roads (written on back of photos), Undated; OR-59 (Box-folder 053/03)
  - Olympic National Forest Roads (written on back of photos), 06-30-1964 thru 07-24-1964; ONF (Box-folder 053/04)
  - Lake Cushman, Washington, 1967-08-12; WFPA-66 (Box-folder 053/05)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington (Negatives), 1972-07-15; 53031 (Box-folder 053/06)
    Film Negatives.
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington (Negatives), 1972-07-15; 53031 (Box-folder 053/07)
    Index available: Yes
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington (Negatives), 1972-07-15; 53031 (Box-folder 053/08)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington (Negatives), 1972-07-15; 53031 (Box-folder 053/09)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1972-07-15; 53031 (Box-folder 054/01)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1972-07-15; 53031 (Box-folder 054/02)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1972-07-15; 53031 (Box-folder 054/03)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1973-07-27; OL-H-73 (Box-folder 054/04)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1977-07-18; OL-77; OL-77A (Box-folder 054/05)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1977-06-06; OL-77; OL-77A (Box-folder 054/06)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1977-07-22; OL-77 (Box-folder 054/07)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1977-07-07; OL-77 (Box-folder 055/01)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 06-11-1977 and 07-23-1977; OL-77 (Box-folder 055/02)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 07-23-1977 and 08-03-1977; OL-77A (Box-folder 055/03)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1979-08-09; 626090 (Box-folder 055/04)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1980-07-07; 626090 (Box-folder 055/05)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1980-05-03; OL-H-80 (Box-folder 055/06)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1982-08-20; 616090A (Box-folder 055/07)
  - Olympic Peninsula, Washington, 1985-08-23; GS-VFHA-C-12 (Box-folder 055/08)
  - Pierce County, Washington, 1978-05-18; NW-78 (Box-folder 055/09)
  - Sumner, Pierce County, Washington, 1978-12-06; S78076 (Box-folder 055/10)
  - Quartz Creek Area, Gifford Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1959-10-02; GP (Box-folder 056/01)
    Scale: 1:32,000
  - Quinalt Indian Reservation (Moclips and Pacific Beach), Washington, 1985-06-18; QIN-85 (Box-folder 056/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3-3 and 5-3
  - Rimrock Area (south and east of Rimrock Lake), Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1966-08-21; ERP-13-6-1 (Box-folder 056/03)
  - Rimrock Area (south and east of Rimrock Lake), Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1966-08-21; ERP-13-6-2 (Box-folder 056/04)
  - Rimrock Area (south and east of Rimrock Lake), Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1966-08-21; REC-13-6-3 (Box-folder 056/05)
    Scale: 1:6,000
  - Rimrock Area (south and east of Rimrock Lake), Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1966-10-31; REC-13-6-5 (Box-folder 056/06)
  - Puget Sound area, Washington, 05-18-1978 thru 08-05-1978; NW-78 (Box-folder 056/07)
  - Eagle Cove, San Juan Island, Washington, 1978-05-31; NW-78 (Box-folder 056/08)
  - San Juan County, Washington, 1963-05-19; ELV (Box-folder 056/09)
  - San Juan County, Washington, 1963-10-01; ELV (Box-folder 056/10)
  - San Juan County, Washington, 10-01-1963 thru 10-11-1963; ELV (Box-folder 056/11)
  - Sequim area, Clallam County, Washington, 1985-06-10; OL-85 (Box-folder 057/01)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-07-23; CWD (Box-folder 057/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1R-
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-07-28; CWD (Box-folder 057/03)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-07-23; CWD (Box-folder 057/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2R-
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-07-23; CWD (Box-folder 057/05)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-07-24; CWD (Box-folder 058/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3R-
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-07-24; CWD (Box-folder 058/02)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-07-24; CWD (Box-folder 058/03)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-07-28; CWD (Box-folder 058/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4R-
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-08-08; CWD (Box-folder 058/05)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-08-08; CWD (Box-folder 058/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5R-
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-08-19; CWD (Box-folder 058/07)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-10-06; CWD (Box-folder 059/01)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956-10-06; CWD (Box-folder 059/02)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1966-05-03; CWD (Box-folder 059/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1GG
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1966-05-03; CWD (Box-folder 059/04)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1966-05-03; CWD (Box-folder 059/05)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1966-09-19; CWD (Box-folder 059/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2GG
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1966-08-20; CWD (Box-folder 059/07)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1967-06-18; CWD (Box-folder 059/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3GG
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1967-06-18; CWD (Box-folder 059/09)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1967-08-29; CWD (Box-folder 059/10)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1967-09-23; CWD (Box-folder 059/11)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4GG
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1967-09-23; CWD (Box-folder 060/01)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1967-09-23; CWD (Box-folder 060/02)
  - Upper Skagit River, Washington, 1960-08-05; WASH 32-H (Box-folder 060/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-24
  - Skagit River, Washington, 1971-08-11; L10382A (Box-folder 060/04)
  - Skagit River, Washington, 1971-08-11; L10382A (Box-folder 060/05)
  - Skagit River and vicinity, Washington, Undated; GSS and CWD (on folder) (Box-folder 060/06)
  - Skagit River and vicinity, Washington, 1941-07-09; GS S (Box-folder 060/07)
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1983-06-07; NW-C-83 (Box-folder 060/08)
  - Snohomish County, Washington, 1983-06-07; NW-C-83 (Box-folder 060/09)
  - Skamania County, Washington, 1955-07-20; GS-VJQ (Box-folder 061/01)
  - Boulder River Rd., Snohomish County, Washington, 1954-07-28; GS-VFE (Box-folder 061/02)
  - Boulder River Rd., Snohomish County, Washington, 1954-08-01; GS-VFE (Box-folder 061/03)
  - Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1952-07-28; GS-QM (Box-folder 061/04)
  - Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1952-07-28; GS-QM (Box-folder 061/05)
  - Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1952-07-28; GS-QM (Box-folder 061/06)
  - Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1952-07-28; GS-QM (Box-folder 061/07)
  - Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1952-07-28; GS-QM (Box-folder 061/08)
  - Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1952-07-28; GS-QM (Box-folder 061/09)
  - Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1952-07-28; GS-QM (Box-folder 061/10)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1953-08-14; BBH (Box-folder 061/11)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1M
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1953-08-14; BBH (Box-folder 062/01)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1953-08-14; BBH (Box-folder 062/02)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1953-08-14; BBH (Box-folder 062/03)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1953-08-14; BBH (Box-folder 062/04)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1953-08-14; BBH (Box-folder 062/05)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1954-05-14; BBH (Box-folder 062/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2M
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1954-05-17; BBH (Box-folder 062/07)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1954-05-17; BBH (Box-folder 062/08)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1954-07-22; BBH (Box-folder 062/09)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1954-05-14; BBH (Box-folder 063/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3M
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1954-05-16; BBH (Box-folder 063/02)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1954-05-16; BBH (Box-folder 063/03)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1954-05-16; BBH (Box-folder 063/04)
  - South Puget Sound, Washington, 1954-10-27; BBH (Box-folder 063/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4M
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, Undated; EMM (Box 064)
    Index sheet of EMM photos compiled by Map Library.
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 064)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 1-5b
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 065)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 6-8a
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 066)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 9-11
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 067)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 12-14
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 068)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 15-17
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 069)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 17-19
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 070)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 20-22
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 071)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 23-26
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 072)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 27-30
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 073)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 31-33b
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 074)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 34-36
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-1964; EMM (Box 075)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 37-38
  - Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1972-07-28; EXQ (Box 075)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 1-4
  - Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1972-07-28; EXQ (Box 076)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 5-9
  - Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1972-07-28; EXQ (Box 077)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 10-14
  - Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1972-08-08; EXQ (Box 078)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 15-21
  - Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1972-08-07; EXQ (Box 079)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 22-28
  - Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1972-08-27; EXQ (Box 080)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 29-31, 33-34
  - Garfield County, Washington, 1969-07-09; CCG-1KK; CCG-4KK (Box 080)
  - Garfield County, Washington, 1970-08-04; CCG-1LL (Box 080)
  - Garfield County, Washington, 1970-08-13; CCG-2LL (Box 080)
  - Chelan - Mt. Baker Project, Washington, 1958-08-28; DR - WR (Box 080)
  - Cowlitz County, Washington, 1982-06-19; OSI-82 (Box 081)
  - Gorge Dam Area, Washington, cross-state highway, 1960-08-05; WASH 32-L (Box 081)
    Scale: 1:3,000
  - Randle - Gifford-Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1966-07-27; COG-66; Western Aerial Contractors (Box 081)
  - Gifford-Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1962-10-17; GP-BD (Box 081)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 1-3
  - Gifford-Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1962-10-17; GP-BD (Box 081)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 4-7
  - Gifford-Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1961-07-09; GPT (Box 082)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines (strips) 1-5, 5RE
  - Gifford-Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1962-07-27; GP2 (Box 082)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 1-26
  - Mt. St. Helens Area, Washington, 1967-06-19; WFPA-64R (Box 083)
  - Gifford-Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1964-09-13; GPFC (Box 083)
    Photo Negative behind photos.
  - Gifford-Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1972-08-25; 53059 (Box 083)
  - Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie and Gifford Pinchot National Forests, Washington (photo negatives), 1972-07-15; 616030; Mark Hurd Aerial Surveys (Box 083)
  - Glacier Peak area, Washington, 1944-10-06; GS-BJ (Box 084)
  - Grant County, Washington, 1955-07-12; AAR (Box 084)
  - Grant County, Washington, 1955-07-12; AAR (Box 085)
  - Grant County, Washington, 1955-07-12; AAR (Box 086)
  - Grant County, Washington, 1961-06-27; AAR (Box 087)
  - Grant County, Washington, 1961-07-02; AAR (Box 088)
  - Grays Harbor County, Washington, 1981-05-28; OL-81; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Box 088)
  - Island County, Washington, 1963-05-19; ELU (Box 088)
    NW-C-76 10A-63 in back of folder.
  - Jefferson County, Washington, 1981-07-04; OL-81 (Box 088)
  - Howard A. Hanson Reservoir, King County, Washington, Undated; CRW-8 (Box 088)
  - Eagle Gorge Reservoir, King County, Washington, 1961-07-20; H-ASCW (Box 088)
  - Lake Marcel area - north of Carnation, King County, Washington, Undated; KC-S-0 (Box 088)
  - Hood Canal area, Washington, 1975-06-09; OL-C-75 (Box 088)
  - King County, Washington, 1978-05-18; NW-78 (Box 089)
  - Kitsap County, Washington, 1978-05-18; NW-78 (Box 089)
  - Klickitat County, Washington, 1969-10-06; KLB-69; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Box 089)
  - Klickitat County, Washington, 1971-05-12; AAS (Box 089)
  - Lewis County, Washington, 1978-06-02; NW-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Box 089)
  - Lewis River, Gifford Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1967-05-15; L70403; Delano Aerial Surveys (Box 089)
    Scale: 1:6,000; 1:12,000
  - Mason County, Washington, 1978-05-19; NW-78; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Box 089)
  - Mt. Baker (U.S.G.S. Project), Washington, 1940-09-21; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Box 090)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 0-4
  - Mt. Baker (U.S.G.S. Project), Washington, 1940-09-21; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Box 091)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 5-10
  - Mt. Baker (U.S.G.S. Project), Washington, 1940-09-21; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Box 092)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 11 and Duplicates
  - Mt. Baker-Wenatchee-Chelan, Washington, 1944-10-07; GS-BJ (Box 092)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 1-6
  - Mt. Baker-Wenatchee-Chelan, Washington, 1944-10-07; GS-BJ (Box 093)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Lines 7-8
  - Mt. Baker – Chelan, Washington, 1947-08-24; GS-CJ (Box 093)
  - Mt. Baker - Chelan, Washington, 1947-09-01; GS-CJ (Box 094)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 44-69 thru 44-90